<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
################################ ACTORS ##########################################
<poster>https://mykodirepo20.000webhostapp.com/Scraper/Icons/poster.jpg</poster>
################################################################################

<dir>
      <title>****************Boss Actor & Actress*****************</title>
    
      <link></link> 
          
      <thumbnail></thumbnail>
          
          
      <fanart></fanart>
        
      <summary></summary>

</dir>



<dir>
        <title>Ice Cube Movies</title>

        <tmdb>person/movies/9778</tmdb>
          
        <animated_thumbnail></animated_thumbnail>
          
        <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/dzdn1tyWkC4EjlBVKvpAhg5osYA.jpg</thumbnail>
          
        <animated_fanart></animated_fanart>
          
        <fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/iG0Nvnql8NpnySQOLQAIOyRl4tR.jpg</fanart>
		
		<summary>Biography
O'Shea Jackson Sr., better known by his stage name Ice Cube, is an American rapper, record producer, actor, screenwriter, film producer, and director. He began his career as a member of the hip-hop group C.I.A. and later joined N.W.A. Monetary conflict with his bandmate Eric "Eazy-E" Wright and manager Jerry Heller caused him to embark on a solo rap career, leading to forays into acting, writing and directing.</summary>

</dir>

<dir>
        <title>Jennifer Lopez</title>

        <tmdb>person/movies/16866</tmdb>
          
        <animated_thumbnail></animated_thumbnail>
          
        <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hNgmDBICnD8La2QN1Pkflh5NJqJ.jpg</thumbnail>
          
        <animated_fanart></animated_fanart>
          
        <fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hNgmDBICnD8La2QN1Pkflh5NJqJ.jpg</fanart>
		
		<summary>Biography
Jennifer Lynn Lopez (born July 24, 1969, height 5' 4½" (1,64 m)), also known by her nickname J.Lo, is an American actress, singer, record producer, dancer, television personality, fashion designer and television producer. Lopez began her career as a dancer on the television comedy program In Living Color. Subsequently venturing into acting, she gained recognition in the 1995 action-thriller Money Train.

Her first leading role was in the biographical film Selena (1997), in which she earned an ALMA Award for Outstanding Actress. She earned her second ALMA Award for her performance in Out of Sight (1998). She has since starred in various films, including The Wedding Planner (2001), Maid in Manhattan (2002), Shall We Dance? (2004), Monster-in-Law (2005), and The Back-up Plan (2010).

Lopez came to prominence within the music industry following the release of her debut studio album On the 6 (1999), which spawned the number one hit single "If You Had My Love". Her second studio album J.Lo (2001) was a commercial success, selling eight million copies worldwide. J to tha L-O!: The Remixes (2002) became her second consecutive album to debut at number one on the Billboard 200, while her third and fourth studio albums – This Is Me... Then (2002) and Rebirth (2005) – peaked at number two on the Billboard 200. In 2007, she released two albums including her first full Spanish-language album Como Ama una Mujer and her fifth English studio album, Brave. With a new record label, Lopez released Love? on April 19, 2011. In 2012, she released her greatest hits album, Dance Again... the Hits. A.K.A. followed in 2014.

Lopez's contributions to the music industry have garnered her numerous achievements including two Grammy Award nominations; two Latin Grammy Award nominations; three American Music Awards, amongst six nominations; and the estimated sale of over 55 million records worldwide. Billboard ranked her as the 27th Artist of the 2000s decade. Lending her musical knowledge to others, Lopez was a member of the judging panel of American reality television competition American Idol.

She led People en Español's list of "100 Most Influential Hispanics" in February 2007. She has parlayed her media fame into a fashion line and various perfumes with her celebrity endorsement. Outside of her work in the entertainment industry, Lopez advocates human rights, vaccinations and is a supporter of Children's Hospital Los Angeles. She currently executive produces the TV show Shades of Blue in which she stars as Harlee Santos, a dirty cop who provides for her daughter with money from bribes and protection payments.</summary>

</dir>

<dir>
        <title>Kevin Hart</title>

        <tmdb>person/movies/55638</tmdb>
          
        <animated_thumbnail></animated_thumbnail>
          
        <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9zxRAhWMxhVrgDnUysvTGLW7fcW.jpg</thumbnail>
          
        <animated_fanart></animated_fanart>
          
        <fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nTYKqSQzJ9VlYKgqoES7WIDHywi.jpg</fanart>
		
		<summary>Biography
Kevin Hart (born July 6, 1979) is an American actor and comedian.

Description above from the Wikipedia article Kevin Hart (actor), licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.</summary>

</dir>

<dir>
        <title>Snoop Dogg</title>

        <tmdb>person/movies/19767</tmdb>
          
        <animated_thumbnail></animated_thumbnail>
          
        <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/qj4dRFASr1LCxFvCg8hZ73ZlO2r.jpg</thumbnail>
          
        <animated_fanart></animated_fanart>
          
        <fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/qj4dRFASr1LCxFvCg8hZ73ZlO2r.jpg</fanart>
		
		<summary>Biography
Calvin Cordozar Broadus, Jr. is an American rapper, singer-songwriter, record producer, and actor, well known by his stage names Snoop Doggy Dogg, Snoop Dogg, and Snoop Lion. He has sold over 30 million albums worldwide.</summary>

</dir>

<dir>
        <title>Tom Cruise</title>

        <tmdb>person/movies/500</tmdb>
          
        <animated_thumbnail></animated_thumbnail>
          
        <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2Dkx4uuGoWFrPSitxdikv9z5azR.jpg</thumbnail>
          
        <animated_fanart></animated_fanart>
          
        <fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/3oWEuo0e8Nx8JvkqYCDec2iMY6K.jpg</fanart>
		
		<summary>Biography
Thomas "Tom" Cruise (born Thomas Cruise Mapother IV; July 3, 1962) is an American actor and filmmaker. He has been nominated for three Academy Awards and has won three Golden Globe Awards.

He started his career at age 19 in the 1981 film Endless Love. After portraying supporting roles in Taps (1981) and The Outsiders (1983), his first leading role was in Risky Business, released in August 1983. Cruise became a full-fledged movie star after starring as Pete "Maverick" Mitchell in Top Gun (1986). He has since 1996 been well known for his role as secret agent Ethan Hunt in the Mission: Impossible film series. One of the biggest movie stars in Hollywood, Cruise has starred in many successful films, including The Color of Money (1986), Cocktail (1988), Rain Man (1988), Born on the Fourth of July (1989), Far and Away(1992), A Few Good Men (1992), The Firm (1993), Interview with the Vampire: The Vampire Chronicles (1994), Jerry Maguire (1996), Eyes Wide Shut (1999), Magnolia (1999), Vanilla Sky (2001), Minority Report (2002),The Last Samurai (2003), Collateral (2004), War of the Worlds (2005), Lions for Lambs (2007), Valkyrie (2008), Knight and Day (2010), Jack Reacher (2012), Oblivion (2013), and Edge of Tomorrow (2014).

In 2012, Cruise was Hollywood's highest-paid actor. Fifteen of his films grossed over $100 million domestically; twenty-one have grossed in excess of $200 million worldwide. Cruise is known for his support for the Church of Scientology and its affiliated social programs. From: Wikipedia.</summary>

</dir>

<dir>
        <title>Bruce Lee </title>

        <tmdb>person/movies/19429</tmdb>
          
        <animated_thumbnail></animated_thumbnail>
          
        <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/kzeeWP2pHcGcyWfUYJOx65DaJlP.jpg</thumbnail>
          
        <animated_fanart></animated_fanart>
          
        <fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/kzeeWP2pHcGcyWfUYJOx65DaJlP.jpg</fanart>
		
		<summary>Biography
Bruce Lee (born Lee Jun-fan; 27 November 1940 – 20 July 1973) was a Chinese American and Hong Kong actor, martial arts instructor, philosopher, film director, film producer, screenwriter, and founder of the Jeet Kune Do martial arts movement. He is widely considered by many commentators, critics, media and other martial artists to be the most influential martial artist of modern times, and a cultural icon. Lee was born in San Francisco to parents of Hong Kong heritage but was raised in Hong Kong until his late teens. Lee emigrated to the United States at the age of 18 to claim his U.S. citizenship and receive his higher education. It was during this time that he began teaching martial arts, which soon led to film and television roles. His Hong Kong and Hollywood-produced films elevated the traditional Hong Kong martial arts film to a new level of popularity and acclaim, and sparked a major surge of interest in Chinese martial arts in the West in the 1970s. The direction and tone of his films changed and influenced martial arts and martial arts films in Hong Kong and the rest of the world, as well. He is noted for his roles in five feature-length films: Lo Wei's The Big Boss (1971) and Fist of Fury (1972); Way of the Dragon (1972), directed and written by Lee; Warner Brothers' Enter the Dragon (1973), directed by Robert Clouse; and Game of Death (1978), directed by Robert Clouse. Lee became an iconic figure known throughout the world, particularly among the Chinese, as he portrayed Chinese nationalism in his films. He initially trained in Wing Chun, but he later rejected well-defined martial art styles, favouring instead to utilise useful techniques from various sources in the spirit of his personal martial arts philosophy, which he dubbed Jeet Kune Do (The Way of the Intercepting Fist).

Description above from the Wikipedia article Bruce Lee, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.

Source: Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia.</summary>

</dir>

<dir>
        <title>Anthony Mackie </title>

        <tmdb>person/movies/53650</tmdb>
          
        <animated_thumbnail></animated_thumbnail>
          
        <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/5VGGJ0Co8SC94iiedWb2o3C36T.jpg</thumbnail>
          
        <animated_fanart></animated_fanart>
          
        <fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/5VGGJ0Co8SC94iiedWb2o3C36T.jpg</fanart>
		
		<summary>Biography
Anthony Mackie (born September 23, 1979) is an American actor. He has been featured in feature films, television series and Broadway and Off-Broadway plays, including Ma Rainey's Black Bottom, Drowning Crow, McReele, A Soldier's Play, and Talk, by Carl Hancock Rux, for which he won an Obie Award in 2002.

He was nominated for Best Supporting Actor at the 2009 Independent Spirit Awards for his role in The Hurt Locker. This is Mackie's second ISA nomination, the first coming for his work in 2003 in Brother to Brother, where he was nominated for Best Actor. Also in 2009, Mackie portrayed rapper Tupac Shakur in the film Notorious. He appears in the 2011 Matt Damon film The Adjustment Bureau where he plays Harry Mitchell, a sympathetic member of a shadowy supernatural group that controls human destiny.

Description above from the Wikipedia article Anthony Mackie, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.</summary>

</dir>

<dir>
        <title>T.I.</title>

        <tmdb>person/movies/76126</tmdb>
          
        <animated_thumbnail></animated_thumbnail>
          
        <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ycNO8wU6H75wDDfojMCTjoxtEmt.jpg</thumbnail>
          
        <animated_fanart></animated_fanart>
          
        <fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ycNO8wU6H75wDDfojMCTjoxtEmt.jpg</fanart>
		
		<summary>Biography
Clifford Joseph Harris, Jr. (born September 25, 1980), better known by his stage name T.I. or T.I.P., is an American recording artist, film & music producer, and occasional actor. He is also the founder and co-chief executive officer (CEO) of Grand Hustle Records.

T.I. has released six studio albums (I'm Serious, Trap Muzik, Urban Legend, King, T.I. vs. T.I.P., Paper Trail, and No Mercy) with latter five being highly successful on the commercial market. He has released such successful singles as "Bring Em Out", "What You Know", "Big Shit Poppin' (Do It)", "Swagga Like Us" (featuring Kanye West, Jay-Z and Lil Wayne), "Whatever You Like", "Live Your Life" (featuring Rihanna), "Dead and Gone" (featuring Justin Timberlake), "Got Your Back" (featuring Keri Hilson) and "That's All She Wrote" (featuring Eminem). He has served three stints in county jail, twice for probation violations and once for a U.S. federal weapons charge. While currently serving 11 months in jail he released his seventh studio album, No Mercy. T.I. has also had successful acting career, starring in the films Takers and ATL.

Description above from the Wikipedia article T.I., licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.</summary>

</dir>

<dir>
        <title>Taraji P. Henson </title>

        <tmdb>person/movies/40036</tmdb>
          
        <animated_thumbnail></animated_thumbnail>
          
        <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rxnEvzGlRBsE94s7lC4cMAiLluH.jpg</thumbnail>
          
        <animated_fanart></animated_fanart>
          
        <fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rxnEvzGlRBsE94s7lC4cMAiLluH.jpg</fanart>
		
		<summary>Biography
Taraji P. Henson (born September 11, 1970) is an American actress, producer and singer. She studied acting at Howard University and began her Hollywood career as guest star on several television shows before making her breakthrough in the movie Baby Boy (2001). In 2005, she starred in Hustle & Flow and played Queenie in David Fincher's The Curious Case of Benjamin Button (2008), for which she received an Academy Award nomination.
In 2016, Time named Henson one of the 100 most influential people in the world on the annual Time 100 list. Henson also released an autobiography titled Around The Way Girl.</summary>

</dir>

<dir>
    <title>[B]Denzel Washington[/B]</title>
    <trakt>https://api.trakt.tv/people/Denzel-Washington/movies</trakt>
	
	<thumbnail>https://walter.trakt.tv/images/people/000/412/658/headshots/thumb/dadb66c463.jpg</thumbnail>
          
    <animated_fanart></animated_fanart>
          
    <fanart>https://walter.trakt.tv/images/people/000/412/658/headshots/thumb/dadb66c463.jpg</fanart>
		
    <summary>Biography
Age 63 BornDecember 28, 1954 in Mount Vernon, New York, États-Unis

Denzel Hayes Washington, Jr. (born December 28, 1954) is an American actor, screenwriter, director and film producer. He first rose to prominence when he joined the cast of the medical drama St. Elsewhere, playing Dr. Philip Chandler for six years. He has received much critical acclaim for his work in film since the 1990s, including for his portrayals of real-life figures, such as Steve Biko, Malcolm X, Rubin "Hurricane" Carter, Melvin B. Tolson, Frank Lucas, and Herman Boone. Washington has received two Academy Awards, two Golden Globe awards, and a Tony Award. He is notable for winning the Best Supporting Actor Oscar for his part in Glory in 1989, and the Academy Award for Best Actor in 2001 for his role in the film Training Day. Description above from the Wikipedia article Denzel Washington, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.</summary>

  </dir>

<dir>
    <title>[B]Tupac Amaru Shakur[/B]</title>
    <trakt>https://api.trakt.tv/people//tupac-amaru-shakur/movies</trakt>
	
	<thumbnail>https://walter.trakt.tv/images/people/000/422/069/headshots/thumb/d007c02c98.jpg</thumbnail>
          
    <animated_fanart></animated_fanart>
          
    <fanart>https://walter.trakt.tv/images/people/000/422/069/headshots/thumb/d007c02c98.jpg</fanart>
		
    <summary>Biography
Age 25 Born June 16, 1971 in East Harlem, New York City, New York, U.S.ADiedSeptember 13, 1996

Tupac Amaru Shakur, best known by his stage names 2Pac and Makaveli was an American rapper and actor. Shakur has sold over 75 million albums worldwide as of 2010, making him one of the best-selling music artists in the world</summary>

  </dir>

<dir>
      <title>Popular People</title>
      <tmdb>people/popular</tmdb>
	</dir>
